Are you a SMART fella,
or a FART smella?
Let's find OUT!
Okay,
a number analogy!
Four makes eleven,
five makes fourteen,
six makes seventeen,
so nine makes...
what?
A.
Twenty-three,
B.
Twenty-six,
C.
Twenty-four,
or D.
Twenty-seven?
Five seconds!
TIME'S UP!
The answer is...
B,
twenty-six!
Each number is multiplied by three
then take away one,
so nine becomes twenty-six.
Check this out,
a word analogy!
Light is to dark,
as fast is to...
what?
A.
Slow,
B.
Night,
C.
Down,
or D.
Late?
Five seconds!
TIME'S UP!
It's...
A,
slow!
Light and dark are opposites,
so the opposite of fast is slow.
Check this out,
fill in the blank!
The riddle was so blank that
it took her all afternoon to
solve it.
A.
Easy,
B.
Silly,
C.
Difficult,
or D.
Short?
Five seconds!
TIME'S UP!
It's...
C,
difficult!
Taking all afternoon means difficult.
So,
are you smart or fart?
Count up your correct answers to
find your rank!
So,
how did you do?
Comment your score below,
and follow for more!